Contact

Vill: Hasnabad, P.O: Dhaka jute mills. P.S: South Keranigonj, District: Dhaka-1311 01303377757 (Mobile) takbirahmed96@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/md-sayedanwar-99935712b (LinkedIn) emergenconsultancy.godaddysites.co (Personal)

Top Skills

Microsoft Office Microsoft Excel Leadership

Certifications

Assessment from pymetrics ICBM 2019-2nd International Conference on Business & Management

Md Sayed Anwar

Performance Marketing | Digital Marketing | E-commerce | SEO | Digital Media & Strategy

Dhaka

Summary

Hi, my name is MD. Sayed Anwar, I am from Dhaka, Bangladesh. I am a digital marketer who likes to meet and interact with people. I love creating effective marketing campaigns for projects I rely on. I am currently working as a Brand Manager at Emergen Consultancy. It is an emerging digital marketing agency dedicated to creating unforgettable experiences for you & your customers.

Experience

Emergen Consultancy
Brand Manager
March 2022 - Present (4 months)

Power house road, Basundhara Riverview, Hasnabad - 1204, Bangladesh

Emerging digital marketing agency dedicated to creating unforgettable experiences for you & your customers.

Key Responsibilities:

- 1. Manage marketing activities and campaigns
- 2. Take part in business performance analysis and present report to top management
- 3. Contributing to the implementation of marketing strategies
- 4. Organize and design marketing activities or events to raise brand awareness
- 5. Support the business team to introduce new products in the market
- 6. Connect market research to identify opportunities for promotion and growth
- 7. Collaborate with managers repairing budgets and wondering expenses
- 8. Craft annual marketing plan for company growth yeah alignment with marketing lead
- 9. Lead creative development to motivate the target audience to "take action"
- Analyze market dynamics to stay competitive and study customer behavior in shaping business strategy

NetSTAR, Inc.

Content Moderator

April 2020 - March 2022 (2 years)

Check and handle the illegal content of the platform, including the pictures, live broadcast, short

video, voice, text etc. responsible for the content safety of the platform.

Proactively find the clues, summarize the features, types, data, information etc. of the illegal content,

and make timely reports.

Collect the illegal key words and add & maintain the regional sensitive vocabulary periodically.

Collect the local cultural customers, policy information and news, and report & feedback in time.

SEBPO

Executive, Digital AD Operations
June 2018 - April 2020 (1 year 11 months)
Bangladesh

I used to create engaging content and am adept at including the natural use of keywords to increase search engine optimization without interrupting the flow of the article. I have promotional newsletters and articles on various subjects related to business and job search questions and have received excellent ratings from my clients. I enjoy conducting the necessary research to make my articles relevant current and interesting and I bring my industry knowledge and experience to every project I tackle.

- 1. Trafficking ads in ad server
- 2. Test all ad tags prior to any campaign going live
- 3. Monitor daily campaign delivery, assist with adjusting or rebooking campaign parameters
- Q/A campaign trafficking by line item to ensure accurate campaign booking in ad servers
- 5. Optimize campaigns based on direction from Campaign Manager, troubleshoot issues with campaign delivery and performance.

Doctorola Ltd.

Marketing Operations Intern

March 2018 - June 2018 (4 months)

House 86, Flat A2, Block D, Road 10/1, Niketan, Dhaka 1212

Analyze market behavior and sales trends and report it to senior executive. Keep updated with Area Sales Officers. Sales track and activation on daily basis.

Field visit whenever needed.

Data entry operator.

BRAC University Marketing Association

2 years 8 months

Head Of Operations

October 2016 - December 2017 (1 year 3 months)

BRAC University UB01, Mohakhali, 66 Bir Uttam AK Khandakar Road, Dhaka 1212

People Management.

Pursue Investors/ funding.

Follow-up team members.

Planning & Implementing and making sure every member has a role into it.

Event development strategies based on analysis, research and feedback.

Director Operations Logistics

May 2015 - September 2016 (1 year 5 months)

BRAC University UB01, Mohakhali, 66 Bir Uttam AK Khandakar Road, Dhaka 1212

People Management.

Planning & Implementing events.

Provide necessary logistics support.

Education

BRAC University

Bachelor's degree, Finance and Marketing (2014 - 2018)

Dania college

Higher Secondary School Certificate, Commerce · (2011 - 2013)

A.K. High School & College

Secondary School Certificate, Business/Commerce, General · (2009 - 2011)